You might remember yesterday we
talked about the IPO of Digit Insurance and today again along with that
we were looking at New India Insurance,
ICICI LBRD, ICICI LBRD
is up by almost 5% today again. A Rajesh Satpute
ICICI LBR tracks this stock,
tell me yesterday and today's move is very strong, now what will happen next.
Harshad ji, in fact this morning we had
given it in our Chart Ka Chamatkar and the
target was the same in the treasury of 1370 1380,
so for those who have taken it, I would
say that you hold it intraday,
definitely book profit but if
someone wants to keep it, then the new stop loss will be
1350 and the target will be 1400 1420.
ICIC LBA moving towards 1420
was a good trade. B Airtel,
he had given a target of 740 and had said that he should
also take a call of 720. I remember he had recommended the call of 720
at around 11 o'clock, let us bring it once,
where has it reached at this time
Trade?  The target of 740 was for futures.
Please call me once with 720.
Director sir, the target was 23 around 1235.
So here also there is some
movement coming, Tata Consumer Products,
this is also a buy trade and
this is also a bullish counter as suggested to you by our experts.
Well, HDFC Life is up 3.5% today.  So before
leaving, there has been a boom in SBI Life also.   Will
Manas take SBI Live or would he prefer to stick
with HDFC Life?
There is no doubt that HDFC is
looking much better on the live charts as it has
given a good move in the last two days.
It is now trading above the 200 moving average.
But now it
is a bit difficult to shop here.  My understanding is that
you might see follow up buying in SBI Life.  The
stock has a resistance at
1320 but the pattern is positive.   The
undertone remains bullish.  Therefore, I
believe that charging should definitely be done here.
Buy at current levels.
You have to keep stop loss below 1284.
In the hope that if the levels of 1320 are broken
then levels up to 1350 will be seen
in SBI L.
We SBI L trading on your screen at 1307.
After a good move,
this stock came into a little rest mood.  It's 1522 with
8 minutes left.  Let us take a look at the
market breath and
try to judge the action in derivatives.  Let's see
what the data we saw in the morning says now?
More close to 18,000
More close to 4,000 What do Bank Nifty
stats say?  What do Nifty stats
say?  What is market breadth
?  These derivatives were 91 advances this morning I think
when I looked at them.
Longs have come down a bit from there now
84 nco first source HPCL bajer
paints pnb so you can see some OMCs here,
metals are visible and
if you see the impact of paint is visible,
mid cap IT is visible, in long build
up baj finst gave super swing,
today after Zee Entertainment earnings,
after a few days the action in it
increased again and ICIC, these are some such stocks where the
trend is at all time high,
where did the long unwinding happen in Coromandel, in Bata,
in Esscosbota, in Chemis and
in Tata Chemicals, in chemical space,
a little profit booking was seen in cable goods today and
short build up PVR Bharat Fauj IGL
Concor Core Mahanagar Gas Sir.